{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995234648","data":{"timestamp":" 946995234648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 166f7012-e4a3-44a7-bc43-a89550512e08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995275974","data":{"timestamp":" 946995275973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 166f7012-e4a3-44a7-bc43-a89550512e08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995276139","data":{"timestamp":" 946995276138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 166f7012-e4a3-44a7-bc43-a89550512e08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995447386","data":{"timestamp":" 946995447385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 166f7012-e4a3-44a7-bc43-a89550512e08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995474857","data":{"timestamp":" 946995474857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995483822","data":{"timestamp":" 946995483820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995488819","data":{"timestamp":" 946995488819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995494170","data":{"timestamp":" 946995494170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995498072","data":{"timestamp":" 946995498072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995505343","data":{"timestamp":" 946995505343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995512584","data":{"timestamp":" 946995512584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995516597","data":{"timestamp":" 946995516597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995522486","data":{"timestamp":" 946995522486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995526892","data":{"timestamp":" 946995526891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995532558","data":{"timestamp":" 946995532558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995536172","data":{"timestamp":" 946995536172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995540057","data":{"timestamp":" 946995540057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995544752","data":{"timestamp":" 946995544752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995548622","data":{"timestamp":" 946995548621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995554451","data":{"timestamp":" 946995554450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995563100","data":{"timestamp":" 946995563099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995568782","data":{"timestamp":" 946995568782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995573179","data":{"timestamp":" 946995573179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995580218","data":{"timestamp":" 946995580218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995584121","data":{"timestamp":" 946995584121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995588067","data":{"timestamp":" 946995588067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995593666","data":{"timestamp":" 946995593665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995600602","data":{"timestamp":" 946995600602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995605537","data":{"timestamp":" 946995605537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995611313","data":{"timestamp":" 946995611312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 9e95a595-009c-4be2-8e2f-1f8f51a0b8f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995626304","data":{"timestamp":" 946995626304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995628414","data":{"timestamp":" 946995628414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995630528","data":{"timestamp":" 946995630527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995633761","data":{"timestamp":" 946995633760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995636041","data":{"timestamp":" 946995636041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995638276","data":{"timestamp":" 946995638276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995641176","data":{"timestamp":" 946995641175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995643427","data":{"timestamp":" 946995643426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995645656","data":{"timestamp":" 946995645656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995648901","data":{"timestamp":" 946995648900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995651007","data":{"timestamp":" 946995651006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995653112","data":{"timestamp":" 946995653111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995656120","data":{"timestamp":" 946995656119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995658353","data":{"timestamp":" 946995658352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995660584","data":{"timestamp":" 946995660583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995663580","data":{"timestamp":" 946995663580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995665865","data":{"timestamp":" 946995665865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995668160","data":{"timestamp":" 946995668160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995671134","data":{"timestamp":" 946995671133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995673248","data":{"timestamp":" 946995673247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995675357","data":{"timestamp":" 946995675356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995678503","data":{"timestamp":" 946995678502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995680715","data":{"timestamp":" 946995680714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995682919","data":{"timestamp":" 946995682918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995686076","data":{"timestamp":" 946995686075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995688508","data":{"timestamp":" 946995688508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995690931","data":{"timestamp":" 946995690930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995694048","data":{"timestamp":" 946995694047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995696333","data":{"timestamp":" 946995696333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995698630","data":{"timestamp":" 946995698629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995701646","data":{"timestamp":" 946995701646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995703892","data":{"timestamp":" 946995703891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995706112","data":{"timestamp":" 946995706111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995709095","data":{"timestamp":" 946995709094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995711463","data":{"timestamp":" 946995711462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995713851","data":{"timestamp":" 946995713850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995717004","data":{"timestamp":" 946995717004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995719369","data":{"timestamp":" 946995719368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995721764","data":{"timestamp":" 946995721763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995724721","data":{"timestamp":" 946995724720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995726991","data":{"timestamp":" 946995726990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995729297","data":{"timestamp":" 946995729296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995732552","data":{"timestamp":" 946995732552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995734836","data":{"timestamp":" 946995734835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995737107","data":{"timestamp":" 946995737106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995740458","data":{"timestamp":" 946995740458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995742210","data":{"timestamp":" 946995742210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995742265","data":{"timestamp":" 946995742264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" 08e0095d-becd-4d1e-88b0-74807c1e8ba0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995769696","data":{"timestamp":" 946995769695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" bc148a77-120f-43ea-8d42-cb70063702bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995805349","data":{"timestamp":" 946995805348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" bc148a77-120f-43ea-8d42-cb70063702bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995805459","data":{"timestamp":" 946995805459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_171343"," gameId":" bc148a77-120f-43ea-8d42-cb70063702bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"end":"end"}]}